Finding aid to Office of the President William Allan Neilson files CA.MS.00013
Smith College Archives
- Series II. Organizations
  - Northampton High School, 1925-39 (Box 398, Folder 16)
  - Northampton School Department, 1921-39 (Box 398, Folder 17)
  - Northampton School for Girls, 1923-38 (Box 398, Folder 18)
  - Northampton State Hospital, 1917-36 (Box 398, Folder 20)
  - Northfield Schools (Northfield Seminary, Mt. Herman School), 1921-37 (Box 398, Folder 21)
  - Northwestern University, 1922-34 (Box 398, Folder 22)
  - O (misc.), 1920-38 (Box 398, Folder 23)
  - Oberlin College, 1922-40 (Box 398, Folder 24)
  - Oregon Agricultural College, 1919-24 (Box 398, Folder 25)
  - P (misc.), 1920-39 (Box 398, Folder 26)
  - Pan American Union, 1926-37 (Box 398, Folder 27)
  - Pennsylvania State Teacher's College, 1932 (Box 398, Folder 28)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1917-26 (Box 398, Folder 29)
  - Periodicals (misc.), A-L, 1920-37 (Box 398, Folder 30)
  - Periodicals- Boston Evening Transcript, 1926-36 (Box 398, Folder 31)
  - Periodicals- Charm Magazine, 1928-34 (Box 398, Folder 32)
  - Periodicals- The Delineator, 1922 (Box 398, Folder 33)
  - Periodicals- Fortune Magazine, 1936 (Box 398, Folder 34)
  - Periodicals- Hampshire Gazette, 1918-38 (Box 398, Folder 35)
  - Periodicals (misc.), M-Z, 1922-32 (Box 398, Folder 36)
  - Periodicals- NewYork Times, 1923-39 (Box 398, Folder 37)
  - Periodicals- the Outlook, 1928-30 (Box 398, Folder 38)
  - Periodicals- Springfield Republican, 1920-38 (Box 398, Folder 39)
  - Periodicals- Southern Churchman, 1929 (Box 398, Folder 40)
  - Periodicals- Women's Home Companion, 1925-32 (Box 398, Folder 41)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Society, 1917-41; undated (Box 399, Folder 1-7)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Society-- Charter Applications, A-O, 1921-25; undated (Box 399, Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Society-- Charter Applications, P-Z, 1924-25 (Box 399, Folder 9)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Society, "The American Scholar", 1932-43 (Box 399, Folder 10-11)
  - Pine Mountain Settlement School, 1920-24 (Box 399, Folder 12)
  - Printers (misc.), 1921-39 (Box 399, Folder 13)
  - Printers- George Banta Publishing Company, 1924-33 (Box 399, Folder 14)
  - Printers- Rumford Press, 1925-32 (Box 399, Folder 15)
  - Printers- Southworth Press, 1924-27 (Box 399, Folder 16)
  - Publishers (misc.), 1915-33 (Box 399, Folder 17)
  - Publishers- Harper and Brothers, 1925-39 (Box 399, Folder 18)
  - Publishers- Houghton Mifflin Company, 1919-35 (Box 399, Folder 19)
  - Publishers- Oxford University Press, 1920-40 (Box 399, Folder 20)
  - Q-R (misc.), 1920-39; undated (Box 400, Folder 1)
  - Radcliffe College, 1921-38 (Box 400, Folder 2)
  - Reed College, 1921-33 (Box 400, Folder 3)
  - Religious (misc.), 1918-35 (Box 400, Folder 4)
  - Religious- Council of Church Boards of Education, 1924-35 (Box 400, Folder 5)
  - Religious-Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America, 1925-35 (Box 400, Folder 6)
  - Religious- Interchurch World Movement, 1919-20 (Box 400, Folder 7)
  - Rochester, University of, 1920-28 (Box 400, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1918-35 (Box 400, Folder 9)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, 1925-28 (Box 400, Folder 10)
  - Rollins College, 1927-35 (Box 400, Folder 11)
  - Rosemary Hall, 1925-33 (Box 400, Folder 12)
  - Russell Sage College, 1929-38 (Box 400, Folder 13)
  - Rutgers University, 1931-39 (Box 400, Folder 14)
  - S (misc.), 1918-39; undated (Box 400, Folder 15)
  - Saint Catherine's School, 1924-32 (Box 400, Folder 16)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1929-38 (Box 400, Folder 17)
  - Scripps College, 1925-39 (Box 400, Folder 18)
  - Sho-Kwo-Sha, Co., 1931 (Box 400, Folder 19)
  - Simmons College, 1927-36 (Box 400, Folder 20)
  - Skidmore College, 1925-36 (Box 400, Folder 21)
  - Smith College Association for Christian Work, 1921-27 (Box 400, Folder 22)
  - Smith College Day School, 1926-38 (Box 400, Folder 23)
  - Smith College Nursery School, 1929-36 (Box 400, Folder 24)
  - Smith College School for Social Work- Permanent Charity Fund, 1918-21 (Box 400, Folder 25)
  - Smith College School for Social Work, 1918-41; undated (Box 400, Folder 26-29)
  - Smith College Student Government Association, 1924-29 (Box 400, Folder 30)
  - Social Hygiene, American S.H. Association Sex Education Study, 1926 (Box 400, Folder 31)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1930-33 (Box 400, Folder 32)
  - Springfield (misc.), 1919-36 (Box 400, Folder 33)
  - Springfield City Club, 1935-39 (Box 400, Folder 34)
  - Springfield Junior Colleges, 1918-34 (Box 400, Folder 35)
  - Stephens College, 1924-38 (Box 400, Folder 36)
  - Student Friendship Fund, 1917-24 (Box 400, Folder 37)
  - Student Third Class Association, 1924-34 (Box 400, Folder 38-39)
  - Students' Aid Society, 1918-39 (Box 400, Folder 40)
  - Students' International Union, 1926-44 (Box 400, Folder 41-42)
  - Sweet Briar College, 1919-39 (Box 400, Folder 43)
  - T (misc.), 1919-36 (Box 401, Folder 1)
  - Teacher's College, Columbia University, 1919-35 (Box 401, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1920-43 (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Texas, University of, 1923-31 (Box 401, Folder 4)
  - Theatre (misc.), 1921-36; undated (Box 401, Folder 5)
  - Theatre- Ben Greet Players, 1930-31 (Box 401, Folder 6)
  - Theatre- Federal Theatre Project, 1935-39 (Box 401, Folder 7)
  - Theatre- the Shakespeare Playhouse, 1920-21 (Box 401, Folder 8)
  - Theatre- Wm B. Feakins, Inc, 1930-35 (Box 401, Folder 9)
  - Trinity College, 1920-38 (Box 401, Folder 10)
  - Tufts College, 1920-37 (Box 401, Folder 11)
  - U (misc.), 1920-36 (Box 401, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Dept of the Interior- Education Bureau, 1918-36; undated (Box 401, Folder 13-14)
  - U.S. Dept of Labor, Bureau of Immigration, 1923-33 (Box 401, Folder 15)
  - University College, Toronto, 1921 (Box 401, Folder 16)
  - University Lecturer's Association, 1917-18 (Box 401, Folder 17)
  - V (misc.), 1918-37; undated (Box 401, Folder 18)
  - Vassar College, 1917-39; undated (Box 401, Folder 19-22)
  - Villa Collina Ridente, 1929-39 (Box 401, Folder 23)
  - W (misc.), 1919-37; undated (Box 401, Folder 24)
  - Weimar-Jenna Summer College, 1931 (Box 401, Folder 25)
  - Wellesley College, 1917-39 (Box 401, Folder 26-29)
  - Wells College, 1920-37 (Box 401, Folder 30)
  - Wesleyan College, 1919-38 (Box 401, Folder 31)
  - Westover School, 1931-39 (Box 401, Folder 32)
  - Wheaton College, 1925-38 (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Wilson College, 1919-36 (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Winthrop College, 1933-35 (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1918-31 (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Woman's, Women's (misc.), 1921-39; undated (Box 402, Folder 5)
  - Women's Colleges- Alumnae Committee of the 7 Colleges, 1928-39; undated (Box 402, Folder 6-13)
  - Women's Colleges- 4-College Conferences, 1917-25 (Box 402, Folder 14-17)
  - Women's Colleges- 5-College Conferences, 1926-37 (Box 402, Folder 18-24)
  - Women's Colleges- 7-College Conferences, 1934-39 (Box 402, Folder 25-26)
  - Women's Colleges- 7-Women's College Advisory Council, 1932 (Box 402, Folder 27)
  - Women's Colleges- 9-College United Publicity Work, 1919 (Box 402, Folder 28)
  - Women's Educational and Industrial Union, 1917-32 (Box 402, Folder 29)
  - Women's Insurance Bureau, 1928-34 (Box 402, Folder 30)
  - Worlds' Fairs, 1934-37 (Box 402, Folder 31)
  - Y (misc.), 1929-32 (Box 402, Folder 32)
  - Yale University, 1919-36; undated (Box 402, Folder 33-34)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1923-39 (Box 402, Folder 35)
- Series III. Subjects
  - Academic Costume, 1925-39 (Box 403, Folder 1)
  - Accidents, 1919-20 (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Administration- Administrative Board, 1922-24; undated (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - Administration- Appointment Bureau, 1923-24 (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Administration- Board of Admission, 1919-39 (Box 403, Folder 5)
  - Administration- Dean, Office of the, 1921-39 (Box 403, Folder 6)
  - Administration- Personnel Office- Correspondence, 1924-39 (Box 403, Folder 7)
  - Administration- Personnel Office- Reports, 1925-33 (Box 403, Folder 8)
  - Administration- Purchasing Dept., 1922-39 (Box 403, Folder 9)
  - Administration- Registrar, 1920-39 (Box 403, Folder 10)
  - Administration- Registrar "Spring Count for Courses", 1937-38 (Box 403, Folder 11)
  - Administration- Treasurer, Budget- Comparative Balance Sheets, 1923-35 (Box 403, Folder 12)
  - Administration- Treasurer, Correspondence, 1918-25 (Box 403, Folder 13-25)
  - Administration- Treasurer, Correspondence, 1925-39; undated (Box 404, Folder 1-3)
  - Administration- Treasurer, Receipts, 1930; undated (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Administration- Treasurer, report on Security Holdings, 1933 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Administration- Trustees, By-Laws, 1925 (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Administration- Trustees, Correspondence, 1920-40; undated (Box 404, Folder 7-10)
  - Administration- Trustees, Special Committee to To Chose a Successor, 1937-38 (Box 404, Folder 11)
  - Administration- Trustees, Special Committee, 1938-39 (Box 404, Folder 12-18)
  - Administration- Vocational Office, 1920-39 (Box 404, Folder 19)
  - Administration- Vocational Office, Annual Report, 1934-35 (Box 404, Folder 20)
  - Administration- Vocational Office, Annual Report, 1937-38 (Box 404, Folder 21)
  - Administration- Vocational Office, newspaper clippings, 1932 (Box 404, Folder 22)
  - Administration- Warden's Office, 1924-42 (Box 404, Folder 23-27)
  - Admission, 1917-34 (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary 1925, (50th) Correspondence, 1923-25 (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary 1925, (50th) Faculty Publications, 1923-25 (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary 1925, (50th) Honorary Degrees, 1923-25 (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary 1925, (50th) News Clippings, 1923-25 (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary 1925, (50th) Planning Committee, 1924-25 (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Bequests, Gifts, Memorials Etc -- General and misc., 1919-39 (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Bequests- Converse, Edmond Cogswell Scholarship, 1921-22 (Box 405, Folder 8)
  - Bequests- Drew, Charles Church, 1919-20 (Box 405, Folder 9)
  - Bequests- Hillyer, Charlotte J., 1919-26 (Box 405, Folder 10)
  - Bequests- Mandelle, Mary S., 1929-30 (Box 405, Folder 11)
  - Bequests- Sage, Olivia Margaret, 1919-20 (Box 405, Folder 12)
  - Bequests- Smart, Elizabeth Allen 1910, 1933 (Box 405, Folder 13)
  - Bicycles, 1930 (Box 405, Folder 14)
  - Black Students, 1927-45 (Box 405, Folder 15)
  - Bookplates, 1922 (Box 405, Folder 16)
  - Bronze Plaques, 1930-31; undated (Box 405, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1922-32 (Box 405, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects Ames and Dodge, 1919-38 (Box 405, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects, general A-Z, 1918-36 (Box 405, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Alumnae House, 1938; undated (Box 405, Folder 21)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects,Branerd, Leeds and Kellog, 1920-21 (Box 405, Folder 22)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects, King and Campbell, 1920-21 (Box 405, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects, Putnam and Stuart, 1922-36 (Box 405, Folder 24)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects Murphy and Dana;Murphy, Mebill and Hamlin, 1920-30 (Box 405, Folder 25)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects Rich and Mathesius, 1922-25 (Box 405, Folder 26)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Architects Milton See and Son, undated (Box 405, Folder 27)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Buildings, list with architects and dates, 1925 (Box 405, Folder 28)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Buildings, Misc., 1919-39; undated (Box 405, Folder 29)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Contractors, 1920-38 (Box 405, Folder 30)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Grecourt Gates, 1922-29 (Box 405, Folder 31)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Grounds, Misc., 1930-39 (Box 405, Folder 32)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Heating, 1920-33 (Box 405, Folder 33-34)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Hillyer Gallery, Additions and Reconstruction, 1918-34 (Box 405, Folder 35)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Housing Lists, undated (Box 405, Folder 36)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Infirmary (1919), 1917-22 (Box 405, Folder 37)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Insurance, Chauncey H. Pierce, 1918-23 (Box 405, Folder 38)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Insurance, Fire- Corr., 1922-25 (Box 405, Folder 39)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Insurance, Fire- Reports and Plans, 1922-23; undated (Box 406, Folder 1-2)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Interiors, Misc., 1922-39 (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Landscape Architect, 1937-39 (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Laundry Building, Correspondence, 1920-25 (Box 406, Folder 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Laundry Building, Contracts, 1921 (Box 406, Folder 6)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Lighting, 1930-39 (Box 406, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds- President's House, Correspondence, 1919-26 (Box 406, Folder 8-11)
  - Buildings and Grounds- President's House, Interior, 1918-33 (Box 406, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quadrangle Houses,General and Misc., 1918-28 (Box 406, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses, Emerson, Jordan, Cushing- Correspondence, 1919-23 (Box 406, Folder 14-19)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses, Emerson House Interior, 1921-22 (Box 406, Folder 20)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses, Gardiner,Morrow, Wilson- Correspondence, 1923-27 (Box 406, Folder 21-22)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses, Jordan House Interior, 1921-22 (Box 406, Folder 23)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses, Comstock, Wilder -Correspondence, 1928-30 (Box 407, Folder 1)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Quad Houses King, Scales Correspondence, 1935-36 (Box 407, Folder 2-6)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Real Estate Correspondence- Belden, Mrs. A.M., Real Estate Agent, 1922-39 (Box 407, Folder 7)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Real Estate Correspondence- Burgess, Mary V. White House Inn, 1921-25 (Box 407, Folder 8)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Cable, Hannah L. Cable Property, 1928 (Box 407, Folder 9)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Cochran, William M. Real Estate Agent, 1924-39 (Box 407, Folder 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Garnett, Ambler. St. John's Church, 1920-21 (Box 407, Folder 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Hudnut, Helen. Real Estate Agent, 1926-36 (Box 407, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Cline, George M., 1922-30 (Box 407, Folder 13)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- misc., 1919-39 (Box 407, Folder 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Pierce, Chauncey H. Real Estate Agent, 1918-31 (Box 407, Folder 15-16)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Schoeneck, M.A.T. 22 Belmont Avenue., 1925-26 (Box 407, Folder 17)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Real Estate Correspondence- Vincens, Berthe. Property at 30 Belmont, 1928-33 (Box 407, Folder 18)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Riding Stable, 1926-29 (Box 407, Folder 19)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Sage Hall Correspondence, 1922-30; undated (Box 407, Folder 20-24)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Sage Hall and Scott Gym, Correspondence, 1922-25 (Box 407, Folder 25-26)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Scott Gym, Correspondence, 1919-27; undated (Box 407, Folder 27-28)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Stoddard Hall, Addition, 1919 (Box 407, Folder 29)
  - Buildings and Grounds- Tryon Gallery, Correspondence, 1924-29; undated (Box 407, Folder 30-32)
  - Chapel, 1920-37 (Box 407, Folder 33)
  - Chime- Dorothea Carlile (ex-1922) Chime, 1918-27 (Box 407, Folder 34)
  - Class...(Class Attendance, Class of), 1921-39 (Box 407, Folder 35)
  - Debating Society, 1925-39 (Box 407, Folder 36)
  - Departments- Course Evaluations (student), undated (Box 407, Folder 37)
  - Departments- Art, general, 1920-39; undated (Box 408, Folder 1-2)
  - Departments- Art, Evaluation Report, 1923 (Box 408, Folder 3)
  - Departments- Art, Evaluation Report Responses, 1923 (Box 408, Folder 4)
  - Departments- Art, Library, undated (Box 408, Folder 5)
  - Departments- Astronomy, 1926-39 (Box 408, Folder 6)
  - Departments- Botany, 1929-39 (Box 408, Folder 7)
  - Departments- Classics, 1919-39 (Box 408, Folder 8)
  - Departments- Chemistry, 1924-39 (Box 408, Folder 9)
  - Departments- Economics and Sociology, 1917-39 (Box 408, Folder 10)
  - Departments- Economics and Sociology, "State of the Department", 1937 (Box 408, Folder 11)
  - Departments- Education, 1921-39 (Box 408, Folder 12-13)
  - Departments-Education Day School and Nursery School, 1927-38 (Box 408, Folder 14)
  - Departments-English, 1918-39; undated (Box 408, Folder 15-17)
  - Departments- French, 1918-39; undated (Box 408, Folder 18-20)
  - Departments- Geology, 1926-39 (Box 408, Folder 21)
  - Departments- Geology, Black Hills Summer Study, 1932-35 (Box 408, Folder 22)
  - Departments- German, 1933-39 (Box 408, Folder 23)
  - Departments- Government, 1928-39 (Box 408, Folder 24)
  - Departments- History, 1918-39 (Box 408, Folder 25)
  - Departments- Hygiene and Physical Education, 1927-40; undated (Box 408, Folder 26)
  - Departments- Italian, 1929-35 (Box 408, Folder 27)
  - Departments- Mathematics, 1928-39 (Box 408, Folder 28)
  - Departments- Misc., 1917-36 (Box 408, Folder 29)
  - Departments- Music, 1918-30 (Box 408, Folder 32)
  - Departments- Music, 1931-39; undated (Box 409, Folder 1-3)
  - Departments- Music, Personnel, 1919-22; undated (Box 409, Folder 4)
  - Departments- Music, Report on Department, 1923 (Box 409, Folder 5-6)
  - Departments- Music, Report on Department, Responses, 1923 (Box 409, Folder 7)
  - Departments- Music, Summer School, 1934-39. undated (Box 409, Folder 8-9)
  - Departments- Philosophy, 1926-39 (Box 409, Folder 10)
  - Departments- Philosophy and Psychology, 1917-18 (Box 409, Folder 11)
  - Departments- Physics, 1921-39 (Box 409, Folder 12)
  - Departments- Psychology, 1926-36 (Box 409, Folder 13)
  - Departments- Psychology, Pre-School Play Group, 1935-36 (Box 409, Folder 14)
  - Departments- Psychology, 1937-39; undated (Box 409, Folder 15)
  - Departments- Religion and Biblical Literature, 1919-39 (Box 409, Folder 16)
  - Departments- Russian, 1932-34 (Box 409, Folder 17)
  - Departments- Spanish, 1918-39 (Box 409, Folder 18)
  - Departments- Spoken English, 1919-39; undated (Box 409, Folder 19-20)
  - Departments- Zoology, 1900-39; undated (Box 409, Folder 21-23)
  - Dietary Studies, 1918 (Box 409, Folder 24)
  - Diplomas, 1926-38 (Box 409, Folder 25)
  - Disappearances, 1925-37 (Box 409, Folder 26)
  - Dramatics, 1919-44 (Box 409, Folder 27)
  - Emergency Fund, 1919-35 (Box 409, Folder 28)
  - Faculty, General, 1917-39 (Box 410, Folder 1)
  - Faculty- Committees (misc.), 1918-37 (Box 410, Folder 2)
  - Faculty- Committees, Course of Study, 1918-36; undated (Box 410, Folder 3-4)
  - Faculty- Committees, Graduate Instruction, 1919-39 (Box 410, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Committees, Lectures, 1928-39 (Box 410, Folder 6)
  - Faculty-Committee on the Selection of Refugee Scholars, 1938-39 (Box 410, Folder 7)
  - Faculty- Committees, Tenure and Promotion, 1925-39 (Box 410, Folder 8)
  - Faculty- Insurance and Pensions, 1919-33 (Box 410, Folder 9)
  - Faculty- Research Reports, 1937 (Box 410, Folder 10)
  - Faculty- Sabbaticals, 1926-32 (Box 410, Folder 11-12)
  - Faculty- Salaries, 1919-33 (Box 410, Folder 13)
  - Faculty- Misc., 1916-32 (Box 410, Folder 14)
  - Financial- Letter to Parents, Drafts and Comments, 1925 (Box 410, Folder 15)
  - Financial- Letter to Parents, Responses, 1925 (Box 410, Folder 16)
  - Food, 1918-29 (Box 410, Folder 17-18)
  - Foreign Students- List, 1917-40 (Box 410, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Students, 1919-40 (Box 410, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Students- Serbian, Correspondence, 1919-20 (Box 410, Folder 21-22)
  - Funds- Four Million Dollar Fund, Correspondence, 1919-26 (Box 410, Folder 23)
  - Funds- Four Million Dollar Fund, Donor Lists, 1919-20 (Box 410, Folder 24)
  - Funds- Four Million Dollar Fund, Misc, 1919; undated (Box 410, Folder 25)
  - Glee Club, 1937 (Box 410, Folder 26)
  - Grades, 1925-28 (Box 411, Folder 1)
  - Health Service Correspondence, 1917-39 (Box 411, Folder 2-3)
  - Health Service- Influenza Epidemic, 1920 (Box 411, Folder 4)
  - Health Service- Physician Reports, 1920-22; 27 (Box 411, Folder 5)
  - Health Service- Psychiatrist Reports, 1925-30 (Box 411, Folder 6)
  - Health Service- Study of Health Service, 1936 (Box 411, Folder 7)
  - Home Economics Misc., 1923-24 (Box 411, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics- American Home Economics Association, 1924-30 (Box 411, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees (general), 1921-39 (Box 411, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates A-B, 1933-38 (Box 411, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates C-F, 1928-35 (Box 411, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates G-H, 1928-39; undated (Box 411, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates, Johnson, Elizabeth Forest, 1937-39 (Box 411, Folder 14)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates K-M, 1933-38; undated (Box 411, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates N-R, 1931-39; undated (Box 411, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates S, 1930-35; undated (Box 411, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Degrees- Candidates, van Kleek, Mary Abby 1904, 1919-22; undated (Box 411, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Degrees- Granted but not Conferred, 1925-39 (Box 411, Folder 19)
  - Honor System, 1918; undated (Box 411, Folder 20)
  - Honors, General Honors, 1924-39 (Box 411, Folder 21)
  - Honors, Special Honors Correspondence and News Clippings, 1921-28 (Box 411, Folder 22)
  - Honors, Special Honors Reporst, memos, drafts, 1922-32 (Box 411, Folder 23)
  - Houses, Housing, 1920-36 (Box 411, Folder 24)
  - Hymn Book, 1920-22 (Box 411, Folder 25)
  - Immigration Act, 1924 (Box 411, Folder 26)
  - Intelligence Test (petition from students), 192? (Box 411, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Students, 1922-39 (Box 412, Folder 1)
  - Junior Year Abroad- England, 1937 (Box 412, Folder 2)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France, 1919-26 (Box 412, Folder 3-7)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Exams and Reports I, 1926 (Box 412, Folder 8)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Exams and Reports II, 1926 (Box 412, Folder 9)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Exams and Reports III, 1926 (Box 412, Folder 10)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France, 1926-29 (Box 412, Folder 11-19)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France, 1930-39 (Box 413, Folder 1-16)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France- Experiences (by students), undated (Box 413, Folder 17)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Correspondence, undated (Box 413, Folder 18)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Lists, Misc., undated (Box 413, Folder 19)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France Misc., undated (Box 413, Folder 20)
  - Junior Year Abroad- France- Paris Property Correspondence, 1924-30 (Box 413, Folder 25)
  - Junior Year Abroad- General, 1925-39; undated (Box 414, Folder 1-2)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Germany, 1931-45; undated (Box 414, Folder 3-14)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Italy, 1929-40; undated (Box 414, Folder 15-20)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Mexico, 1935-41 (Box 415, Folder 1-2)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Scotland, 1935-38 (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Spain, 1930-37 (Box 415, Folder 4-6)
  - Junior Year Abroad- Switzerland, 1928-39 (Box 415, Folder 7)
  - Juniper Lodge- Correspondence, 1924-38; undated (Box 415, Folder 8-9)
  - Juniper Lodge- General and Misc., 1925; undated (Box 415, Folder 10)
  - Laundry, 1918-33 (Box 415, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Parents, 1921-30; undated (Box 415, Folder 12)
  - Library, 1917-36 (Box 415, Folder 13-17)
  - Library Expansion, 1936 (Box 415, Folder 18)
  - Library, 1937-39; undated (Box 415, Folder 19-21)
  - Library- Want List, undated (Box 415, Folder 22)
  - Misc., 1917-39 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Museum, 1917-39; undated (Box 416, Folder 2-11)
  - Museum- List of Art Works, 1915 (Box 416, Folder 12)
  - Museum- Hillyer Gallery, 1918-22 (Box 416, Folder 13)
  - Museum- Lists, 1915-32; undated (Box 416, Folder 14)